CYRIL ICHTI

PHP / JavaScript Developer- Referent Trainer

06.58.66.55.14

cyril@seeren.fr

www.seeren.fr

Lyon



PROFILE

Referent trainer of the Master 2 Designer Application Developer I share the experience accumulated by practicing technology watch.

Interested by Javascript, WebGL, Hybrid, PHP, Python, Java and Android I rely on a conceptual retreat to practice empiricism and develop my cross-functionality.

SKILLS

JavaScript



LINKS



Fnac

fnac.com/e360580/SEEREN



GitHub

github.com/seeren



Google Play

store/apps/developer?id=Seeren



Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/cyril-ichti

EXPERIENCES

2017-2019 | M2I - Referent Trainer CDA Master 2

Animation of training modules, pedagogical engineering, candidate tracking, assessments, publication of materials and coordination of consultants.

2011-2019 | Seeren - PHP/JavaScript Engineer

Founder of Seeren, application development, web penetration tester, profiling and performance audit.

2010-2011 | LGCI - Web Developer

Website development, template creation and integration, print design and animation of web training.

2006-2010 | Freelance - Trainer

Animation of web training, production and computer-assisted design, web integrator during my studies.

CERTIFICATIONS

2018 | PSM1 - Scrum Master Professional



scrum.org/user/421856

2016 | ZCPE - Zend Certified PHP Engineer



zend.com/en/yellow-pages/ZEND028549

EDUCATIONS

2008-2011 | National High School of Architecture

Studies in Architecture, Mathematics, Geometry and Drawing.

2006-2008 | High School of Arts and Crafts

Designer of furniture, space and scenography.

2005-2006 | Paul Valery University

Human sciences, anthropology and ethnology.